siterra.com 2015-06-19

# Privacy Policy - Accruent

###  Effective Date: June 26, 2014

This privacy statement describes how Accruent, LLC (“Accruent”) collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: [www.accruent.com](http://www.accruent.com/) and through our services: 360Facility and Siterra by Accruent, LLC ("Accruent"). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged Accruent. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy.

Accruent has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) and the [TRUSTed Cloud Program Requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/TRUSTed-cloud/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through the web site: www.accruent.com and the services: 360Facility and Sitera does not cover information that may be collected through our mobile web sites.

TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at 512.861.0726. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request).

Accruent complies with the U.S. – E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S. - Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Accruent has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Accruent’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

###  Personal Information We Collect and How We Use It

We collect the following personal information from you if you choose to submit it via an online form

  * Contact Information, such as name, email address, and phone number
  * Demographic Information, such as Industry
  * Product Interest Preferences
  * Credit card and payment information to process transactions with you

We use this information to

  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Respond to a request for a demonstration of our services
  * Send you product or industry information via marketing communications
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
  * Engage in certain transactions with you
  * Process certain transactions with you

###  Service Provider Collection and Use

Accruent collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes.

###  Marketing Communications

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s) or additional marketing communications, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. If you no longer wish to receive these communications, you may follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in the emails you receive.

###  Service Providers

We use other third parties such as an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf and an employment management provider and a credit card processing provider to process payments for certain transactions. When you sign up for our services, we will share your personal information only as necessary for the third party to provide that service.

###  Legal Disclosure

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.
  * if Accruent is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets,  you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

###  Access to Personal Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete/deactivate it by emailing our Customer Support at vang@accruent.com or by contacting us via the postal mail at the contact information listed below.  We will respond to your request for access within 30 days.

Accruent will retain personal data we process on behalf of our client for as long as needed provide services to our client. Accruent will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

###  Choice

We collect information for our Clients, if you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the client that you interact with directly.  If you are a Client and would like to update your account please contact us at vang@accruent.com. We will respond to your request within 30 business days.

###  Access to Data Controlled by our Clients

Accruent has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to Accruent’s Client (the data controller). If the Client requests Accruent to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 business days.

###  Tracking Technologies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies through tracking codes employed by Marketo and Google Analytics. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.

Cookies are used to track a visitor’s activity on our site, from the pages they enter from to the multiple pages on the site they visit to the forms they complete. We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

The use of cookies by our partners and service providers is covered by our privacy statement. We do/do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners and service providers use session ID cookies to to communicate the results to Accruent as their client.

###  Google Analytics

We have implemented the features of Google Analytics for Display Advertising (Demographic and Interest Reporting). These features allow us to review anonymous (non-personally-identifiable) data regarding the age, gender and interests of our website users. This data allows us to adapt our website content to better meet the needs of our users and to improve our marketing efforts.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Network Display Network ads  using the Google Ads settings or via <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>.

###  Clear Gifs

We employ or Marketo employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

###  Social Media Features and Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

###  Links to Third Party Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Accruent. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.

###  Testimonials

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at vang@accruent.com.

###  Public Forums

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at vang@accruent.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

###  Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as login credentials) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at vang@accruent.com.

###  Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

###  Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at vang@accruent.com or via postal mail at 10801-2 N. Mo-Pac Expressway Suite 400, Austin, TX 78759.
